NIGERIAN ELECTIONS MAY LIKELY BE...
As we continue to pray for the upcoming Nigerian Presidential Elections,
let us remember the words of Prophet T.B. Joshua on Sunday February 10, 2019, as quoted in an article:
"The Nigerian election may likely be postponed because of many challenges.
In whatever way, God is in control...
God will not allow anything to happen to Nigeria.
It is just a cloud that is hovering. Be calm.
The nation has a strong bond with God. Nigeria will stand.
Those who will cause trouble will see trouble and those who will cause peace will see peace
but the nation Nigeria will stand."
T.B. Joshua
Sunday February 10, 2019 - Emmanuel TV
RV: Mel Flowers 06/04/2019